{
    "id": "9850bee42f43492c98d0067642dd169f",
    "title": "Questions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".............................. old is your sister?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a3744eabe3c459a813ebdf0bd5175da"
        },
        {
            "question": "'................................... is your mother?' 'My mother is a doctor.'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5bb0f7dc5ab448886ece97f00240e55"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. does your father work?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2933f8ced2a442bd87d4740b188f1a5f"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. is your brotherâ€™s name?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "283540209d5f4b048403ee5734dd8f09"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ you like science fiction?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Has",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79e9cb0aeaca4210ba288e4083786824"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. gave you this watch?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b9b72fa5e7a483d9d3e9180080aca5b"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. do you spend your holidays?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da3eabbdb72b48a39fe7ef26932a1bfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... is your favorite writer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "What",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bccb259942974e229a531b67b8143669"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... you collect stamps?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0ab5d822f594061976039c2132b1422"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. brothers and sisters do you have?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How many",
                "How much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f23a9c462994085b95b7dabb368df85"
        }
    ]
}